Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Baker, Liz; L.A.J. Staff Portraits; Mayer Olga; Morgan, Marjie (Bike); Trio Arete, 2009- (Box-folder 44-71)
- Portraits Blesi, Lauren; CAMP Cohort Group Portrait; Christopherson, Aaron; classes of 1958/59 Group Portraits: Denman, Anne; Gaudino, James (Studio) Graham-Roseburg, Kim; Hall, Dennis; Hubbard, Mari; Sandberg, Annette, 2009- (Box-folder 44-72)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 44-73)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 44-74)
- OPR Snow Shoe RD 800 Blewett Pass, 2012- (Box-folder 44-75)
- Bite, 2012- (Box-folder 44-76)
- Wildcat Dash, 2012- (Box-folder 44-77)
- Move In Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-78)
- Move In Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-79)
- Discover Orientation Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-80)
- Discover Orientation Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-81)
- Miscellaneous: School Spirit 1940's-1960's Archive Scans, Concept shots, president's Power Point Images, Schlanger Scans, 2012- (Box-folder 44-82)
- Events: Longboard competition 04/2012, majors Fair, No place Untouched Exhibit 06/2012, OPR Spring Symposium 04/2012, Wildcat Day 05/2012 (Box-folder 44-83)
- Miscellaneous: computer Science Class, Evening of recognition05/2012, Samuelson Union Tour 04/2012 (Box-folder 44-84)
- Classroom: Backlund, Phil; Kovalerchuk, Boris; Smith, Michael; Staab, Tony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-85)
- Miscellaneous: HC PEP Rally by Kara Jones, Latino/a Welcome, 2012- (Box-folder 44-86)
- Orchesis Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-87)
- Orchesis Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-88)
- Fall Mall Shots, 2012- (Box-folder 44-89)
- Miscellaneous: Archivist at Work Photo, Faculty Banners on Campus, Studio 231 Gallery, West Star Roping Event, 2013- (Box-folder 44-90)
- COB Awards Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-91)
- COB Awards Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-92)
- Fall Blood Drive KC Photos, 2013- (Box-folder 44-93)
- Fall Music Photos for Sarah Carroll, 2013- (Box-folder 44-94)
- Fall Operation ELF, 2013- (Box-folder 44-95)
- Portraits IT Security Staff, McCoy, Amy Student Trustee; Palm, Melanie; Wellington 3D Stills, 2013- (Box-folder 44-96)
- Miscellaneous: Green Screen Item Shots, Snow, Barge Touch Screen, Window Washer, 2013- (Box-folder 44-97)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 3, 2008- (Box-folder 44-98)
- Homecoming: Wellington's Wildfire, HC Decor Contest Doorways, Alumni Awards Banquet, 2008- (Box-folder 44-99)
- Miscellaneous Portraits; Communications Luncheon, E.M.T. Group, Gray, Jen; Hall, Ellen; Janney, Keisha; Hubbard, Mari EMPO; Moreno, A.; Mumma, A.; Music Faculty Scheffelmaier, Jody; Silva, Gini; Spolelstra, Michoan, 2008- (Box-folder 44-100)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Rainbow shots, Washoe, Chalk Wellington, computer Student Shots, Drexler, J.; Frankenfield, C.; Gladen, K.; Harbaugh, J.; Holter, S.; Johnston, A.; Lambert, C.; Nethery, V.; Saunders, P.; Stewart, S.; Villacres, R., 2007- (Box-folder 44-101)
- DHC and Regular Students Hanging Out and Studying, 2008- (Box-folder 44-102)
- Soccer, 2002- (Box-folder 44-103)
- Football, 2002- (Box-folder 44-104)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Marching Band Spells "JM", bailey, J.; Busch, L.; Camarillo, K. (KC); Crawford, A.; Jacobson, B.; Mack, R.; Nover, M.; Sweeney, D.; Tidd, R.; Wind Ensemble/ Performance Shots, 2008- (Box-folder 44-105)
- Fall Classes: Biology Lab, Eckland, A. Textiles Lab; Lupton, N.; Nelson, J. Biology Lab, 2008- (Box-folder 44-106)
- Fall Classroom: Sorey, T. SCI Class; Wahle, C. IT Class, 2008- (Box-folder 44-107)
- Homecoming: Bowers, B. (Mime Performance), McIntyre, J. (Retirement Reception), 2008- (Box-folder 44-108)
- McIntyre Interview Series Student Health/Counseling Staff Shots, 2008- (Box-folder 44-109)
- Career Services " Cool" Group Shot N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 44-110)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Central Connections, 2008- (Box-folder 44-111)
- Bankston, Stacey; Claasen/Hubbard; Corona; Dugmore, Owen; Ford, Robert; Hubbard, Dale and Stephanie; Kitty Moe; Koons, C.; McIntyre/Smith; Underwood/McIntyre, 2008- (Box-folder 44-112)
- Wenatchee Center: Students in Class, Fitch/Plourde Portraits, 2008- (Box-folder 44-113)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Alumni/ S.S. Columns, McIntyre, Jerilyn Science Building, Graeber-Pigeon, N. Class and Port, Laura Jones Class, 2008- (Box-folder 44-114)
- Jerilyn McIntyre Reflection and Interview Shots, 2008- (Box-folder 44-115)
- Miscellaneous Portraits Bankston, S.; Bennet, B. Press Conference; Corona; Dantzler, S.; Dawson, K.; Denman, Anne.; Dining Employees: Ford, R.; Hubbard, Dale and Stephanie; Jackson, Mike; Johnson, Kirk; Kitty Moe; Koons, C.; Luke; McIntyre/Smith; Mumma, A.; Orchesis portraits: Pappas, J.; Sadler, Shirley; Underwood, McIntyre, 2008- (Box-folder 44-116)
- Class Shots: Andonie, R. Comp. Sci Class; Gumaer, J. Elect. Eng. class; Hull, A. Student Teacher Elementary Class, 2008- (Box-folder 44-117)
- Miscellaneous Portraits, Speaking Events: Ronald Beline Mendes; Anne Denman; Amy Mumma; Orchesis Headshots; Wayne Quirk; Salman Rushdie; Cornel West, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 44-118)
- Jim and Lillian Brooks, 2007- (Box-folder 44-119)
- Homecoming Events Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 44-120)
- Homecoming Events Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 44-121)
- Construction Management Students with Dave Carns, Construction Site, 2005- (Box-folder 44-122)
- Housing Groups Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 44-123)
- Housing Groups Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 44-124)
- Housing Groups Disc 3, 2007- (Box-folder 44-125)
- Marji Morgan, Bill Ventrees, 2007- (Box-folder 44-126)
- George Bellah with Taiwan Puppet, Sherer Holter, David Valdez, 2007- (Box-folder 44-127)
- Moses Lake Flight Tech Shots: Brian Roy, Chale Salas, Chris Miller, 2007- (Box-folder 44-128)
- Opera Headshots, 2007- (Box-folder 44-129)
- Portraits: Beacon Images, Karen Blair, Carrie Burke, Camp Staff Dev. Staff Portraits 2007 Distinguished Professors, Dr. Horsley, Rapport Photos, Fisher, Jessica Lee St. Louis, C. Kehner, C.O.B. Honors Images CWU retirees, Student comm. Speaker Lunch D. Thomas, Val Stockwell, Wildcat Shop Staff (Box-folder 44-130)
- Hikers: McCutcheon Student dig., 2007- (Box-folder 44-131)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: CTED Group Frasca, J; Hyatt, J.; Lowery, R.; Sanden N., 2007- (Box-folder 44-132)
- Dance Cats Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 44-133)
- Dance Cats Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 44-134)
- Glady's Cardiff Poetry Reading Music Recital Hall, 2006- (Box-folder 44-135)
- Jerilyn McIntyre with Students at SURC, 2006- (Box-folder 44-136)
- Jerilyn McIntyre with Students at SURC, S.O.U., 2006- (Box-folder 44-137)
- Emily Ward Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 44-138)
- Emily Ward Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 44-139)
- Mugs Girls Basketball and Cross Country, 2006- (Box-folder 44-140)
- Rod McKenna, 2006- (Box-folder 44-141)
- Profs Teaching Disc 1: John Bryant-AFROTC, Tim Burnham-Anatomy, Patsy Callaghan-Discussion, Quenby Delgado-Lecture, George Drake-Lecture, Roxanne Easley, 2006- (Box-folder 44-142)
- Profs Teaching Disc 2 Rodney Laszlo-ROTC, Teresa Sloan-lecture, Jeff Snedeker-Horn Practice, Allen Vautier-Lecture, Amy hoover-Flight Sim, Dale Wilson-lecture, Alex Young-ASL Lecture, 2006- (Box-folder 44-143)
- Profs Teaching Disc 1: Bryant. J.; Burnham, T. (Anatomy); Callaghan, P.; Drake, G.; Easley, R.; Lazslo, R. (ROTC), 2006- (Box-folder 44-144)
- Profs Teaching Disc 2: Sloan, T.; Snedeker, J. Conducting Brass Practice; Weaver, A. (Flight Simulator); Young, A. (ASL), 2006- (Box-folder 44-145)
- Fall Campus Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 44-146)
- Alumni Art Show, 2010- (Box-folder 44-147)
- Miscellaneous: Kollmeyer Water Coloring, Tav Booth 6 Carved Bricks, wind in the Trees/Motion/Blues Skies, 2010- (Box-folder 44-148)
- Teaching/Classroom: Flight Simulators- Canadair Regional Jet Baron, 2010- (Box-folder 44-149)
- Fall Central Connections: Residence Life, 2010- (Box-folder 44-150)
- Homecoming Alumni Events: 1961 Reunion Dinner, Football Game, 2011- (Box-folder 44-151)
- BIS Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 44-152)
- BIS Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 44-153)
- Homecoming Disc 1 Football Game/Events, 2010- (Box-folder 44-154)
- Homecoming Disc 2 Football Game/Events, 2010- (Box-folder 44-155)
- Miscellaneous Heesacker, Gary; Iniguez, Simone Parke Creek counselor; Lee, Jeff Hawaii geology trip; Nimnicht, Jim, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 44-156)
- Portraits Orchesis portraits, Retro Potential trio, ROTC groups in Nicholson, Squeochs, Moses; SURC table shots of Students, Turner, Josh, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 44-157)
- Retro Potential: Peacock, Curtis; Poplin, Meylinda; Smith, Bret, 2010- (Box-folder 44-158)
- Portraits Winter/Spring: ASCWU BOD, AHO, Mary; Benson, Kelly; Clark, George; COB Dean's Council; Jeffery-Petersen, Naomi; Camarillo, Kevin (KC)- breakfast; Kilgore, Kristi; Levine, Marilyn; Singh, Vijay; Varnum, Brad, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 44-159)
- Classroom: Michel, John-Cello Studio Class, 2011- (Box-folder 44-160)
- Miscellaneous people Spring: Distinguished Professors-Singh, Vijay; Cummings, Bobbi; Abdallah, Laila; Rosell, Sharon; Empire Group/Individual- Wang, Fen COB Class, 2011- (Box-folder 44-161)
- Alumni Awards, 2011- (Box-folder 44-162)
- Alumni Awards, Hogue Hall, 2011- (Box-folder 44-163)
- Miscellaneous: STEP Science Class-Jackson/Braunstein, Wind Ensemble Portrait and Performing, Women's Studies, 2011- (Box-folder 44-164)
- Classroom: Smith, Bret-Cello; Arango, Clay and Bulosan, Clarissa-Englehorn Pond with Frog, 2011- (Box-folder 44-165)
- Classroom: Bellah, Trish; Harbaugh, John- Trumpet, 2011- (Box-folder 44-166)
- Perez, Mark-P.E. Class outdoors; Singh, Vijay-vocal Jazz 1 Rehearsal; Takei, Hideki- Kittitas County Historical Museum Trip, 2011- (Box-folder 44-167)
- Classroom: Daquisto, Debra-Workout Class; Henschell-Pellett, Heidi-P.E. class; Young, Therese-Dance Class, 2011- (Box-folder 44-168)
- Fall portraits: Caoile, Nikolas and Melissa; Domingo, Emma; Fu, Ping; Hammond, Megan; Hussman, Steve; Page, Joann; Provaznik, Bill; RA Groups 9/2011- Steiner, Kylie; Varnum, Dawn; Women's Basketball Huddle- Wu, Coco (Box-folder 44-169)
- Fall Portraits: ASCWUBOD Studio shots on White, Camp Staff and Cohorts, 2011- (Box-folder 44-170)
- Music Miscellaneous: Prep Strings Students Teaching Kids 10/2011; Singh, Vijay-vocal Jazz 1 Rehearsal 03/2011; Women's Chorus Portrait 10/2011 (Box-folder 44-171)
- Anne Johansen/Doug Tangen: Shots at Wild Horse Wind/Solar Farm, 2011- (Box-folder 44-172)
- Fall C.O.B. E.O.C.- Savoian, Roy; Mitchell, John; Markell, Eric; Sheffels, Evan; Wollmuth, Duane; West, John; Raha, Arun, 2011- (Box-folder 44-173)
- Miscellaneous People Spring: Green Screen Students- Bittman, Mark; Nimnicht, Jim; Heesacker, Gary, 2011- (Box-folder 44-174)
- Portraits Winter: Athletic Hall of Fame Scans- Ames, Elaine; Baker, Jack; Boivinn, Alan; Bookstore Staff- Chodowicz, Agnieszka, Douglas, Steve; Gass, Michael; Krieble, Cynthia; la Shier, Sean; Mc Kenzie, Rob; Neshyba, Natalie; Rice, Rebecca; Shiver, Todd; Smith, Margaret; Stinson, Jeff; Weber, Kelsey; Wheeler, Sandy; Wickman, Ryan, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 44-175)
- Mt. Rainer Archaeology Field School Disc 1- McCutcheon, Patrick, 2011- (Box-folder 44-176)
- Mt. Rainer Archaeology Field School Disc 2- McCutcheon, Patrick, 2011- (Box-folder 44-177)
- Mt. Rainer Archaeology Field School Disc 3- McCutcheon, Patrick, 2011- (Box-folder 44-178)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 1 Wanecheck, Gerard-light shirt; Matthes, Whitney; Pitts, Mike-flannel shirt; Mclean, Jamey-vest, 2011- (Box-folder 44-179)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 2 Wanecheck, Gerard-lIght shirt; Matthes, Whitney; Pitts, Mike-flannel shirt; Mclean, Jamey-vest, 2011- (Box-folder 44-180)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 3 Wanecheck, Gerard-lIght shirt; Matthes, Whitney; Pitts, Mike-flannel shirt; Mclean, Jamey-vest, 2011- (Box-folder 44-181)
- Geology 502 Disc 1: Mount Saint Helens Field Trip, Wendy Bohrson, 2011- (Box-folder 44-182)
- Geology 502 Disc 2: Mount Saint Helens Field Trip, Wendy Bohrson, 2011- (Box-folder 44-183)
- Fall Miscellaneous: Biology Students Coring Sunrise Lake at Mount Rainier, Challenge Course, 2011- (Box-folder 44-184)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Johansen, Anne/Uribe, Adriana Chemistry Lab, Smith, Bret/Lashier Sean Cello, 2011 Senior Lineman: Ward, Chris (Box-folder 44-185)
- Winter Miscellaneous: Fouts, 03/2011Roger Last Class; 01/2011 Gaudino State of the University; 02/2011 Smith, Carlo with Students (Box-folder 44-186)
- Green Screen at the SURC Students Full Length, Raw Captures, 2011- (Box-folder 44-187)
- Green Screen Student Shots-Final Extractions, 2011- (Box-folder 44-188)
- Green screen Studio Students 03/2004 Raw Captures, 2004-2011 (Box-folder 44-189)
- Koushik Ghosh: At Table with Students Teaching, 2011- (Box-folder 44-190)
- Portraits: Alumni/Student Group Shots, NW Economic Games group, Provost council Group; Martell, Kathryn and Savoian, Roy, 2012- (Box-folder 44-191)
- Classroom: Michael Chinn Wood Working, Sahri Stoddard Painting, Wildcat FB Players Reading to Elementary Children, 2012- (Box-folder 44-192)
- OPR Rock Climbers Disc 1: Frenchman Coulee, 2012- (Box-folder 44-193)
- OPR Rock Climbers Disc 2: Frenchman Coulee, 2012- (Box-folder 44-194)
- OPR Rock Climbers Disc 3: Frenchman Coulee, 2012- (Box-folder 44-195)
- Portraits: Burvee, Toni; Farrell, Jan; Hoisington, Kara; Hopkins, Ryan; Mason, Marilyn; McPherson, Marc; Melton, Brian; Mounsey, John; Olsen, Kim; Page, Joann; Vagina Monologue headshots, 2012- (Box-folder 44-196)
- IET: Dave Carns Soil Compaction lab, 2012- (Box-folder 44-197)
- IET Class: Dave Carns Soil Compaction Lab, 2012- (Box-folder 44-198)
- Beacon Portraits: Jenkins, Zabrina; Swanson, Trish; Wade, Scott; Wind Ensemble, 2012- (Box-folder 44-199)
- Rugby Prom Dresses Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-200)
- Rugby Prom Dresses Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-201)
- COB Dean's Council Portraits, 2012- (Box-folder 44-202)
- Portraits: Boushey, David; COB Dean's Council- Wheeler, Sandy, 2012- (Box-folder 44-203)
- Athletics: Studio Portraits, John Picha Football Practice, 2012- (Box-folder 44-204)
- RA Group/ individual Portraits, 2012- (Box-folder 44-205)
- PANGA Field School Devil's Lake, Oregon Melbourne, Tim Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-206)
- PANGA Field School Devil's Lake, Oregon Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-207)
- PANGA Field School Devil's Lake, Oregon Disc 5, 2012- (Box-folder 44-208)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: 2011-2012 ASCWUBOD, 2012 Discover Leaders; Auslander, Mark; Barlow, Kathleen; Byham, Richard; Cohen, Ken; Conwell, Kevin; Cordner, David; Depaepe, James; Egger, Ann; Fowler, Edie; Kerns, Liz; Liu, Chris; Schmidt, Rhonda; Scott, Shane; Swager, Sara, Vadnais, Teresa; Vaughn, Kevin; Whelan; Burvee (Box-folder 44-209)
- Portraits: Badgley, Margaret; Busalacchi, James; Crawford, Holly; Gabriel, Anthony; Klyve, Dominic; Lambert, Connie; Launius, Michael; Leslie, Emily; Lonowski, Dale; Lunstrum, Lucinda; Martell, Katheryn; Mather, Gertrude-Scans; Sires, Lindsey; Snedeker, Jefferey; Ward, Chris; Williams, Connie, 2012- (Box-folder 44-210)
- Fall Miscellaneous Portraits; COB Faculty- Hydrovolts-Soldier/ Charlie Pringle ;Midstate/ CWU Aviation Group; Minor Nate/ Jackson, Mike-Laser Lab; Orchestra Group at Old Hospital, 2012- (Box-folder 44-211)
- Fall Miscellaneous Portraits: Camp Staff/ individual; Dickerson, Andre; Egger, Anne; Linell, Kari; Strings Faculty; Yarwood, Bill; Fowler, Edi; Kinnan, Shari; Linnell, Kari; Lonowski, Dale; Tosch, Bill, 2012- (Box-folder 44-212)
- Miscellaneous: Dean hall Artwork' Ellensburg/CWU Sign at South End of main, Kairos Quartet, 2012- (Box-folder 44-213)
- Portraits: Goodenberger + Dillenback, IET Faculty/Staff, Student "Thanks" Portraits, 2012- (Box-folder 44-214)
- Miscellaneous Events: Faculty Contract Signing 1013, State of the University 1013, Source 513, 2013- (Box-folder 44-215)
- Fall CWU Car, 2013- (Box-folder 44-216)
- Rally to Stadium CWU Homecoming, no date- (Box-folder 44-217)
- Spring Miscellaneous Events: Alpine Tower, Nimnicht Scholar launch KC Shots, Showcase of Action, 2013- (Box-folder 44-218)
- BackUp Rock Climbers at Frenchman's Coulee Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-219)
- Fall Wildcats from Around the Globe, 2013- (Box-folder 44-220)
- Fall Wildcat Welcome Weekend Cup and Brunch, 2013- (Box-folder 44-221)
- Fall Jordan Lake, 2013- (Box-folder 44-222)
- ROTC JBLM Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 44-223)
- ROTC JBLM Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 44-224)
- Homecoming Disc 1 5K Cancer Run, PEP Rally, Tailgating, Alumni Events, Football Game, 2012- (Box-folder 44-225)
- Homecoming Disc 2 5K Cancer Run, Pep Rally, Tailgating, Alumni Events, Football Game, 2012- (Box-folder 44-226)
- Homecoming Disc 3 5K Cancer Run, Pep Rally, Tailgating, Alumni Events, Football Game, 2012- (Box-folder 44-227)
- IET Open House: Open House, IET Stock Imagery, 2012- (Box-folder 44-228)
- Fall Events: COB Economic conference 10/2012, Wellington's Wildfire 10/2012 (Box-folder 44-229)
- Commencement Disc 1: Christine Day, Convocation, AM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-230)
- Commencement Disc 2: AM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-231)
- Commencement Disc 3: AM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-232)
- Commencement Disc 4: PM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-233)
- Commencement Disc 5: PM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-234)
- Commencement Disc 6: PM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-235)
- Commencement Disc 7: PM Ceremony, 2012- (Box-folder 44-236)
- Commencement Disc 8: convocation, Facebook Pics, 2012- (Box-folder 44-237)
- Fall: OPR Opening, 2013- (Box-folder 44-238)
- Fall: Parade of Nations, 2013- (Box-folder 44-239)
- Fall: Mary Grupe Grand Opening, 2013- (Box-folder 44-240)
- Fall: Día de Los Muertos, 2013- (Box-folder 44-241)
- Fall: Men's Choir, 2013- (Box-folder 44-242)
- Fall: Mr. and Mrs. Central and Wellington Wildfire, 2013- (Box-folder 44-243)
- Fall: Wildcat Welcome Weekend BBQ, 2013- (Box-folder 44-244)
- Fall: WareFare, 2013- (Box-folder 44-245)
- Fall: Trees/ Fall, 2013- (Box-folder 44-246)
- Fall: Swim Tournament, Fall Trees, 2013- (Box-folder 44-247)
- Fall: Holiday Extravaganza, Warefare, 2013- (Box-folder 44-248)
- Fall: Halloween Concert, 2013- (Box-folder 44-249)
- Fall: FB Omlstead Clean Up, 2013- (Box-folder 44-250)
- Fall: ROTC Vigil, 2013- (Box-folder 44-251)
- Spring: bike Rally, Rock Against Rape, Sam Reed, We Speak, 2012- (Box-folder 44-252)
- Charboneau, Jeff Teaching in Zillah Classroom Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-253)
- Charboneau, Jeff Teaching in Zillah Classroom Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-254)
- Greene, Trevor: Toppenish Highschool Principle, CWU Alumni, 2013- (Box-folder 44-255)
- October: Alumni Awards, 2013- (Box-folder 44-256)
- Classroom: Klyve, Dominic math; Jackson, Michael physics/ Laser lab; Surplus- Moffat, Dave and Bakeman, Jason, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 44-257)
- Portraits: Class of 1963 Reunion 06/2013; Delgado, Elvin; Evening of Honorees: Johnson, Joseph; Martinez, Annalillia (Box-folder 44-258)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: CTEA/ FASA Group shots- Gordon, Gene; Greene, Trevor and Charboneau, Jeff; Lillquist, Karl; Schactler, Linda; Schedler, Christopher; Thomas, Debbie, Voice Faculty, 2013- (Box-folder 44-259)
- Fall Miscellaneous Portraits: Camp Group/ Individuals- Crawford, Ashlie; Filler, Angela; Herman, Dan with Student in office; Peacock, Curtis with Student and tubas; Rugby men/Women Headshots-Smith, Margaret; Stochosky, Joy; Wickstrom, Stephanie, 2013- (Box-folder 44-260)
- Distinguished professors Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-261)
- Portraits: COB Dean's Council, COB Faculty, Mid State Aviation/CWU Group with Planes, 2013- (Box-folder 44-262)
- Kathryn Chavez Shots: January/February ASCWU BOD Monday MTG, Campus dine and Tote, Crab Feed 01/2013, Family Literacy Night 01/26-02/23 Tournaments, Faculty Jazz Concert 01/29, Open Mic Nights- The Seafarers 02/2013, The Vagina Monologues, wedding Expo 01/07, Mardi Gras Dinner, Sold! Anti-Slavery Exhibit (Box-folder 44-263)
- Discover Orientation- Villacres Photos Disc 7, 2013- (Box-folder 44-264)
- Dar Memorial 12/2012, Faculty Art Show 02/2013, Herbert Bird memorial 11/2012, MLK March 01/2013, Warefair 12/2012, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 44-265)
- Fall Classroom: Eckland, Andrea; Rosell, Sharon 10/2013; Lee, Alejandro (Box-folder 44-266)
- Eckland, Andrea Roller Derby "Professor Pain" Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-267)
- Eckland, Andrea Roller Derby "Professor Pain" Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-268)
- August Ernest Kris 190, Mammals 813, 2013- (Box-folder 44-269)
- Fall Miscellaneous: Housing group Portraits; Student Accounting committee, Science Students Each at Valley View, Chapman- Stockwell, Valerie EMPMO, 2013- (Box-folder 44-270)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Bite of the Burg, Game Day T-Shirt Shots, Movers and Shakers, 2013- (Box-folder 44-271)
- Miscellaneous Photos: ARC Ribbon Cut, CWU Subaru Roundy/Prater, Christmas Gifts in President's Office, Wall chargers, Whitfield, Raymond Visit with President Gaudino, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 44-272)
- Douglas Honors College, 2013- (Box-folder 44-273)
- Dr. Roxanne Easley Picks, 2013- (Box-folder 44-274)
- Distance Professors Scans, 2013- (Box-folder 44-275)
- Fall Diversity Club, 2013- (Box-folder 44-276)
- Miscellaneous: 01/2013 FLL Robotics Tournament, 03/2013 FRC Robotics Tournament, 01/2013 Mt. Stuart Elementary MLK event, 03/2013 Raining Jane Concert in SURC pit, 12/2012 VEX Robotics Tournament, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 44-277)
- Family and Consumer Science Classroom Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-278)
- Family and Consumer Science Classroom Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-279)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-280)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-281)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 3, 2013- (Box-folder 44-282)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 4, 2013- (Box-folder 44-283)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 5, 2013- (Box-folder 44-284)
- Discover Orientation by Katherine Chavez Disc 6, 2013- (Box-folder 44-285)
- Hall of Fame, 2013- (Box-folder 44-286)
- Wildcat Weekend BBQ, 2013- (Box-folder 44-287)
- Wildcat Weekend Disc 2: New Student Convocation RV, Wildcat Cup Katherine Chavez, 2013- (Box-folder 44-288)
- Campus Malls, Architecture: Late Night Architectural Shots, Ogden, Michael Vid Cam Class Outdoors, OPR Spring Symposium, Outdoor Class on Lawn, ICAT Mitchell Decoration, 2013- (Box-folder 44-289)
- COB Profs Teaching: Iyengar, Deepak; Provaznik, Bill, 2013- (Box-folder 44-290)
- Miscellaneous: 05/2013 Arabs, Persians and Muslims Panel, 05/2013 EMP Impact Kickoff, 05/2013 Evening of Recognition,07/2013 Georgia Pacific SHM Classroom, 02/2013 MLK, 04/2013 National Instruments Lab View, 07/2013 Quest Science Camp (Box-folder 44-291)
- Fall Boo Central by Katherine Chavez, 2013- (Box-folder 44-292)
- Katherine Chavez Shots: 20's Speakeasy Swing Dance, Apple Bowl, Jazz Combo Night, General Shots, NWA Wrestling, 2013- (Box-folder 44-293)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2013- (Box-folder 44-294)
- Commencement Disc 2, 2013- (Box-folder 44-295)
- Commencement Disc 3, 2013- (Box-folder 44-296)
- Commencement Disc 4, 2013- (Box-folder 44-297)
- Fall: Career Fair, 2013- (Box-folder 44-298)
- Wildcat Dash, 2013- (Box-folder 44-299)
- February: Lincoln Student Teachers, 2014- (Box-folder 44-300)
- College of Business, 2014- (Box-folder 44-301)
- Sakura Matsuri-Japanese Cherry Blossom Festival, 2014- (Box-folder 44-302)
- Library Gala: An Evening at Brooks Library, 2014- (Box-folder 44-303)
- COB Awards, 2014- (Box-folder 44-304)
- Distance Professors Alumni Awards, 2014- (Box-folder 44-305)
- Kittitas County: Rock Climbers, Snowmobiling, 2012-2015 (Box-folder 44-306)
- Back Up: Rock Climbers at Frenchman Coulee Disc 2, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 44-307)
- Winter Boots n' Cats, 2014- (Box-folder 44-308)
- COB Awards2014 May: CWU Night at the Mariners (Box-folder 44-309)
- Wildcat Shop Products, 2014- (Box-folder 44-310)